Finding Aid for the Actors' Laboratory Records LSC.1064
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Reports from Actor's Workshop to Executive Board., 1945-1947. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Veteran's Administration
  - Correspondence re Veteran's Administration, veterans as actors at Actor's Lab., 1945-1946. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence re Veteran's Administration., 1946.; Note inside old file reads: Anything placed in this file should have duplicate copy in student's file. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between Actors Lab and Veteran's Administration re students., 1946. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Actors Lab and Veteran's Administration re students., 1946-1947. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Contract, October 1, 1948. (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, contract for education and training.
  - Correspondence, contract, change in curriculum, Veteran's Administration., 1947-1949. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Paid Vouchers for purchases and services, memorandum of payment., 1947-1948. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Contracts., 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, description of acting courses, contract with Veteran's Administration, Proposal for Vocational Rehabilitation Training.
  - Correspondence., 1945-1948. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Correspondence to Veteran's Administration re Curriculum for Veteran.
  - Paid Vouchers for purchases and services other than personal., 1945-1946. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Paid Public vouchers for purchases and services other than personal., 1946. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Paid Public vouchers for purchases and services other than personal., 1946. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Paid Vouchers. Correspondence, public vouchers for purchases and services., 1946-1947. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Paid vouchers for tuition, books, supplies, and equipment., 1947. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Students., 1946. (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Theatre Committee., 1945-1946. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Minutes of Executive Board Theatre Committee Meeting, Agenda. Duplicates.
- Bulletins, minutes of Actor's Lab Council, 1945.; Fragile carbon papers. Some duplicates. (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Theatre Committee Minutes., 1944. (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Lab Council Minutes, 1946. (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Scripts. Scripts, Notes on material compiled for Bernard Shaw Meeting., n.d.; Fragile carbon papers, creased, yellow papers. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Membership List., n.d.; Fragile, creased, yellow papers. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Lists of Members, Union Affiliation, names & addresses. Material may be confidential.
- Insurance & Valuable Papers., 1948.; File created by collator. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Leases Las Palmas, Insurance Policies, Police Permits, Musart.
- Three Little Booklets/Pamphlets: The Wizard of Oz, A Catalogue of One-Act Plays, The Complete Minstrel Guide., 1947.; File created by collator. (Box 9, Folder 2)
- The Dragon. A Wonder Play in 3 Acts by Lady Gregory., 1920. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Workshop Programs., 1944-1948. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- The Curtain Call., 1948.; Torn, yellow sheets. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Newsletter entitled Curtain Call, Workshop Craftsman re Interviews With Jessica Tandy, Sam Levene; staff, functions, organization; World Theatre Survey.
- Actor's Lab Embossing Stamp., n.d.; Item is not in a folder. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Script: The House of Bernarda Alba
  - Script entitled The House of Bernarda Alba, Bernard Alba. 1936. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Script entitled The House of Bernarda Alba, 1936.; Duplicate. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Script entitled The House of Bernarda Alba, 1936.; Third Copy. (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Executive Arm Minutes., 1948-1949. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Minutes of Executive Arm Meetings, Correspondence re Executive Arm.
- Lawsuit (Palermo V.Harper)., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Legal documents (3 copies) Palermo V. the Charles F. Harper Company. Contains the Summons.
- Large black scrapbook honoring the graduating class of 1948, newsclippings, photographs, certificates, miscellaneous documents., Newsclippings are pasted to pages of book, yellow fragile edges of pages. Folder not possible for this item. (Box 17, Folder 1)